Guide to the Donald Gordon Papers, 1900-1988 UA.90.F46
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Modern Art Exhibitions, 1900-1916, II.
  - Brussels, February 22, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Paris, February 28, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Vienna, March-May 1906 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Basel, March 14, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Paris, March 14, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Paris, March 20, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Berlin, Spring 1906 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Budapest, Spring 1906 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Paris, March 26, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Prague, April 15- May 17, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Paris, April 15- June 30, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Dresden, May-October 1906 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Cologne, May 1906 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Paris, May 1, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - Paris, May 4, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - Paris, May 19, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - Rotterdam, May 24, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - Munich, June 1906 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - London, June- July 1906 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Weimar, Summer 1906 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Milan, July 1, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Berlin, October 1906 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Paris, October 6, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Paris, October 25, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - London, November-December 1906 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Vienna, November-December 1906 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Paris, November 9, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Weimar, November 11, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Berlin, after November 15, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Berlin, December 1906 (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Paris, Decmber 4, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - Budapest, Winter 1906-1907 (Box 9, Folder 146)
  - St. Petersburg, Winter 1906-1907 (O.S.) (Box 9, Folder 147)
  - Rotterdam, December 22, 1906- January 20, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 148)
  - Moscow, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Prague, 1907 (?) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Berlin, January 1907 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Vienna, January- February 1907 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Paris, January 10-19, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Paris, January 14, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Paris, January 21, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Paris, February 7-15, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Paris, February 5, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Paris, February 11, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Budapest, March 1907 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Vienna, March- April 1907 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Strasbourg, March 2, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Brussels, March 3, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Paris, March 11, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Paris, March 20, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Berlin, Spring 1907 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Budapest, Spring 1907 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Paris, March 25, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Moscow, March 31- May 12, 1907 (N.S.)/ March 18- April 29, 1907 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Bielefeld, April 1907 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - London, April 1907 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Amsterdam, April-May 1907 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Amsterdam, April 1- May 15, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Paris, April 8, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
  - Pittsburgh, April 11- June 13, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Paris, April 14- June 30, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Paris, April 22- May 8, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Venice, April 22- October 31, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Paris, April 30, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Budapest, May 1907 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cologne, May 1907 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - London, May- June 1907 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Paris, May 1, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Stuttgart, May 1, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Mannheim, May 1, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Düsseldorf, May 11, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Munich, June 1- end of October, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Paris, June 3, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Paris, June 17, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Paris, Summer- end of October 1907 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Amsterdam, July 1907 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Ostende, July 1907 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Weimar, August 1907 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Paris, September 1, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Budapest, Fall 1907 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - London, Fall 1907 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Prague, October- November 1907 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Paris, October 1, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Paris, October 24, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Paris, November 4-16, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Paris, November 14, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Berlin, December 1907 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Budapest, December 1907 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Paris, December 10, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Paris, December 16, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Budapest, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 58-59)
  - Rome, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Moscow, early 1908 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - New York, January 2, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Paris, January 6, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Paris, January 6-18, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Paris, January 8-31, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Berlin, January 8, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Moscow, January 28, 1908 (N.S.)/ December 27, 1907 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - New York, February 3, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Bremen, Mid-February 1908 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Paris, February 17, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Munich, March 1908 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Brussels, March 1, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Berlin, Spring 1908 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - London, Spring 1908 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Paris, March 20, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 75-76)
  - St. Petersburg, April 6, 1908 (N.S.)/March 24, 1908 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - New York, April 6-25, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Paris, April 15- June 30, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - St. Petersburg, April 18- May 24, 1908 (N.S.) (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Paris, April 27, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Pittsburgh, April 30- June 30, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Vienna, after April 1908 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Vienna, May- October 1908 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Prague, May 1, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Amsterdam, May 3, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 86)
  - St. Petersburg, May 8, 1908 (N.S.)/ APril 25, 1908 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Liege, May 9, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Munich, May 15- end of October, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Paris, May 18, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Prague, June- July 1908 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Paris, June 1, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Brussels, June 6-28, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Budapest, Summer 1908 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - London, July-August 8, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Paris, July 3, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Amsterdam, September 1908 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Kiev, Fall 1908 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Berlin, October 1- November 1, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Paris, October 1, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Paris, October 12, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Paris, November 9, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 102-103)
  - Paris, November 11, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Paris, November 23, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Paris, November 25, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Berlin, December 1908 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Munich, December 11, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Paris, December 11, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Paris, December 14, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Paris, December 21, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 111-112)
  - Moscow, late 1908 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Budapest, winter 1908-1909 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Moscow, Winter 1908-1909 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - St. Petersburg, Winter 1908-1909 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Milan, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - St. Petersburg, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Budapest, early 1909 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - New York, January 1909 (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Paris, January 18, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Paris, January 23, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Moscow, January 24-February 28, 1909 (N.S.)/ January 11- February 15, 1909 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Amsterdam, February 1909 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Budapest, February- March 1909 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Paris, February 1, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - New York, February 12, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Berlin, February 28, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Stockholm, March 1909 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Paris, March 1, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Brussels, March 7, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Berlin, Spring 1909 (Box 10, Folder 132)
  - St. Petersburg, Spring 1909 (O.S) (Box 10, Folder 133)
  - Paris, March 22, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Paris, March 25, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - New York, March 30, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 136)
  - London, April 1909 (Box 10, Folder 137)
  - Prague, April- May 1909 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - St. Petersburg, April 7-21, 1909 (N.S.)/ March 25- April 8, 1909 (O.S.) (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Bremen, April 11- May 8, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - Amsterdam, April 11- May 16, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 141)
  - Paris, April 15- June 30, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - New York, April 22, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 143)
  - Venice, April 22, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Pittsburgh, April 29- June 30, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Vienna, May-October 1909 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Paris, May 3-15, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - New York, May 8, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Düsseldorf, May 15- October 3, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Düsseldorf, May 15- October 30, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - London, May 22, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Paris, May 24, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Paris, June 8, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Brussels, June 12- July 4, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Paris, June 21, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - London, July 1909 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Brussels, July 10, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hagen, August 4- September 16, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Amsterdam, October- November 1909 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Munich, October 1909 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Vienna, October-November 1909 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Paris, October 1, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Paris, November 2, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Paris, November 8, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Paris, November 13, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Berlin, November 27, 1909- January 9, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Munich, December 1-15, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Paris, December 6, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Odessa and Kiev, Decmber 17, 1909 (N.S.)/ December 4, 1909 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - New York, December 20, 1909 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - London, Winter 1909 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Moscow, Winter 1909-1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Moscow, Winter 1909-1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Vilna, WInter 1909-1910 O.S. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Brussels, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Budapest, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Florence, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Göteborg, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Kiev, 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - St. Petersburg, 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Stockholm, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Budapest, January-February 1910 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Moscow, January 9- February 13, 1910 (N.S.)/ December 27, 1909- January 31, 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Paris, January 10-22, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 35-36)
  - Paris, January 24, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Prague, February-March 1910 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Berlin, February 5, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - New York, February 9, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Paris, February 14, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Paris, February 21, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - New York, February 21, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Christiana, March 1910 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - St. Petersburg, March 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Paris, March 7, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - New York, March 9, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Brussels, March 12, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Paris, March 15, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Paris, March 18, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Berlin, Spring 1910 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - New York, March 31, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Stockholm, April 1910 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Budapest, April- May 1910 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Paris, April 4, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Paris, April 15- June 30, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Florence, April 20- May 15, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Venice, April 23, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Amsterdam, April 24- beginning of June, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Paris, April 28, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Brussels, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Berlin, May-June 1910 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Prague, May- June 1910 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Budapest, May- September 1910 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Kazan, May 1-14, 1910 (N.S.)/ April 18- May 1, 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Paris, May 2-14, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Paris, May 2-14, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Pittsburgh, May 2- June 30, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - St. Petersburg and Riga, May 2- June 7, 1910 (N.S.) (St. Petersburg)/ June 25- July 20, 1910 (N.S.) (Riga) (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Hamburg, May 14, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Paris, May 16-28, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Paris, May 17, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Munich, May 18- October 31, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Munich, May 18- October 31, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Paris, May 30, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Riga, June 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Paris, June 1-17, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Rotterdam, June 11, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Paris, June 20, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - London, Summer 1910 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - London, July 1910 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Brussels, July 2-25, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Düsseldorf, July 10, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Dresden, September 1910 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Stockholm, September 1910 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Munich, September 1-14, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Rotterdam, September 22, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Leipzig, October 1910 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Paris, October 1- November 8, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Berlin, October 1- December, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Paris, October 15- November 5, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Berlin, October 25, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Vienna, November-December 1910 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Berlin, November 1910- January 1911 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Paris, Nvember 7, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - London, November 8, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - New York, November 18, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Odessa, December 1910 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Moscow, December 1910- January 1911 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Paris, December 4, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Paris, December 19, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - London, Winter 1910 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Moscow, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 103-104)
  - St. Petersburg, January 1911 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Berlin, January- February 1911 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Prague, January- February 1911 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - New York, January 11, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Paris, January 23- February 1, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Vienna, February 1, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Berlin, February 1911 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - New York, February 2, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Paris, February 13, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - New York, February 23, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Berlin, March 1911 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - London, March 1911 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - New York, March 1, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Munich, March 3- April 20, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Paris, March 13, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Brussels, March 18, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Berlin, Spring 1911 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Moscow, Spring 1911 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - St. Petersburg, Spring 1911 (O.S.) (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Paris, March 27, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - New York, March 28, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Christiana, April 1911 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Stockholm, April 1911 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Budapest, April-May 1911 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Paris, April 16- June 30, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Paris, April 21, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Paris, April 24, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh, April 27- June 30, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Amsterdam, April 30, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Leipzig, May 10, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Munich, May 16- October 31, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Barcelona, after May 16, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Paris, May 17, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cologne, May 26, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Amsterdam, June 1911 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - London, June 1911 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Göteborg, after June 1, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Paris, June 6, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Brussels, June 10, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Brussels, June 10- July 3, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Essen, June 13- July 2, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Budapest, summer 1911 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - London, summer 1911 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Paris, June 26, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - London, July 1911 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Domburg, July 1911 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Paris, July 6- October 15, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Paris, July 20- August 5, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Christiania, August 1911 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Cologne, October 1911 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Berlin, October 1911 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Paris, October 1, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Amsterdam, October 6- November 5, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Paris, October 16, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Berlin, November 1911 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - London, November 1911 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Berlin, November-December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Budapest, November- December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Paris, November- December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Vienna, November- December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Paris, November 13, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Berlin, November 18, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Paris, November 20, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Paris, November 27, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Moscow, November 28, 1911 (N.S.)/ November 15, 1911 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Berlin, December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - London, December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Munich, December 1911 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Munich, December 1911- January 1912 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - New York, December 9, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Paris, December 4, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Paris, December 11, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - St. Petersburg, December 17, 1911 (N.S.)/ December 4, 1911 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Moscow, December 21, 1911 (N.S.)/ December 8, 1911 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - London, Winter 1911-1912 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Dresden, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Ekaterinodar, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Paris, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Newark et. al., 1912-1913 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - St. Petersburg, early 1912 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Budapest, January 1912 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - London, January 1912 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Moscow, Jauary 1912 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Berlin, January- February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Prague, January- February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Vienna, January- February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Vienna, January- February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - St. Petersburg, January- February 1912 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Paris, January 22- February 3, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Cologne, January 23, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Munich, February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Munich, February 1912 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Bremen, February 1, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Paris, February 5, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Paris, February 5, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - New York, February 7, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - New York, February 27, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Paris, February 28, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Berlin, March 1912 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Prague, March- April 1912 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - London, March 5, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Brussels, March 9, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Paris, March 11, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Berlin, March 12, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - New York, March 14, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Paris, March 20, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Berlin, Spring 1912 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Vienna, Spring 1912 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - St. Petersburg, Spring 1912 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Moscow, March 24- April 21, 1912 (N.S.)/ March 11- April 8, 1912 (O.S.) (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Berlin, April 1912 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Berlin, April 1912 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - London, April- May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Vienna, April- May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Leipzig, April 7, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Berlin, April 12, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Amsterdam, April 13, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Paris, April 14- June 30, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Paris, April 15-29, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Paris, April 15-27, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Barcelona, April 20, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - London, April 23, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Venice, April 23, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Pittsburgh, April 25- June 30, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Paris, April 29, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Berlin, May 1912 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Berlin, May-June 1912 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Paris, May 1-15, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Paris, May 1-15, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Dresden, May 1-15, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Brussels, May 20, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Cologne, May 25, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Paris, May 29- June 8, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Cologne, June 1, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Brussels, June 1-23, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Rouen, June 15, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Paris, June 17, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - London, summer 1912 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - London, July 1912 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Domburg, July-August 1912 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Hagen, July 2, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Zurich, July 7, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Frankfurt, July 18, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - The Hague, August 1912 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Weimar, August 1912 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Hamburg, August- September 1912 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Munich et. al., September 1912 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Prague, September-November 1912 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Prague, September 22- October 20, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Munich, October 1912 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - St. Petersburg, October 1912 (O.S.) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Berlin, October 1912 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Paris, October 1, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - London, October 5, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Amsterdam, October 6- November 7, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Paris, October 10, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Paris, October 28, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Berlin, November- December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Budapest, November-December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Berlin, November 2, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Munich, November 4, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Amsterdam, November 10, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Paris, November 11, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Paris, November 25- December 7, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Paris, November 25- December 7, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Berlin, November 26, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Hagen, December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - London, December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Moscow, December 1912 (O.S.) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Vienna, December 1912 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Moscow, December-January 1912 (O.S.) (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - London, WInter 1912 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Moscow, Winter 1912-1913 (O.S.) (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Christiania, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Hamburg, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Hamburg, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Prague, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Munich, Winter 1913 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Berlin, January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Berlin, January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Budapest, January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Cologne, January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - London, January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Berlin, January-February 1913 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Budapest, January- February 1913 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Düsseldorf, January-February 1913 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Vienna, January- February 1913 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Vienna, January- February 1913 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - St. Petersburg, January- February 1913 (O.S.) (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Paris, January 17, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Berlin, January 19, 1913 (Box 13, Folder 46)